http://thesemcogroup.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Privacy Policy
You are hereHome › Privacy Policy
The SEMCO Group makes every effort to honor the preferences of our Web site users concerning the collection and use of personally identifiable information. This statement describes how the SEMCO Group collects and uses personally identifying information of visitors to our Web sites.This privacy statement covers the following sites operated by the SEMCO Group: http://www.semco-eng.com, http://www.semco-eng.net, and other SEMCO Group sites that can be accessed through our main site. We encourage you to take the time to read this privacy statement and those of any Web site you visit.  What Information is Collected In general, when you visit our Web sites and access information, you will remain anonymous. For some services provided through our Web sites, we will ask you to register using online registration forms. A registration form will ask for information both about the company to be registered and the individual employees who will use our online services as representatives of the company. For some Web site services, you will be asked to provide a password and user identification.This information is collected to confirm eligibility for use of the online services, to establish the identity of the company and authorized users, and for business contact purposes. Some services available on our Web sites involve the purchase (or sale) by Web site visitors of SEMCO Group equipment or parts. If you elect to engage in transaction opportunities on our Web sites, you will be asked to provide information necessary to facilitate transactions such as shipping address and payment instructions.In addition to information you provide, the SEMCO Group may collect information about your use of our Web sites that will help SEMCO Group improve its online services, such as information regarding what pages you access on our sites, what URL you just came from and the URL you next go to, what browser you are using and your IP address. This information may be used to analyze trends and statistics and monitor link usage.The SEMCO Group may use cookies on some portions of its Web sites. A cookie is an identifier that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. Cookies enable us to provide you with a better experience by allowing us to understand what areas of the Web site are of interest to our visitors.The SEMCO Group may also use cookies when you register to use one of our web-based services. In this situation, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return to visit us. The SEMCO Group can only read cookies from the SEMCO Group Web sites. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our Web sites. If you choose to post messages in message areas or to provide feedback or send an e-mail to us, we may keep a record of that posting or correspondence. Information you disclose in a public message area will naturally be available to and shared with other visitors to our Web sites.  How We Use Information The SEMCO Group may use your information for its own marketing purposes. This may include providing you with information targeted to your interests. We will give you the opportunity to elect not to receive direct-marketing materials from us.The SEMCO Group does not sell any personally identifiable information. When you place an order or make an offer to participate in a transaction opportunity, we will use your personally identifiable information to facilitate the transaction. The SEMCO Group may also maintain transaction history information about our Web site users.The primary use of your information is to enable the SEMCO Group to deliver specific services or products you request or to complete a transaction initiated by you. During the course of completing a transaction initiated by you, the SEMCO Group may provide your contact or other information to a trading partner or other party to the transaction (e.g., financier or bank transferring funds). Again, information you disclose in a public forum will naturally be public and available to other visitors to our Web sites. To the extent "you disclose your information to other parties, their use of the information will not be subject to this privacy statement."Applicant Data The SEMCO Group may use the information that you provide and any other information which is subsequently provided (the “Information”) in considering you for a specific position and/or other available positions at any SEMCO Group location.Your Information may remain active for up to six months and may be kept on record for a limited period of time as required by law. Your Information is stored on a server in the United States of America and is visible to all SEMCO Group locations globally, including countries where laws may not protect data privacy to the same extent as laws in the country or region in which you live. If your submission is considered for employment, it will be used for these purposes only and normally considered primarily in locations where the position(s) is available.The contact details of the SEMCO Group can be found at or via http://www.semco-eng.com. If you become or currently are a SEMCO Group employee, your Information will be retained in individual employment records kept by the SEMCO Group. Such Information will be used in administering benefits and performing the SEMCO Group's contractual and other legal obligations. By submitting your Information, you acknowledge and agree that the SEMCO Group will retain such Information for the purposes mentioned above and consent to such use.Data SecurityThe SEMCO Group uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. Unfortunately, it is impossible to absolutely guarantee the security of data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network.Therefore, although we take reasonable measures to protect your information, the SEMCO Group cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from online services and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will use industry standard efforts to ensure its security on our systems.If the SEMCO Group provides links to third party sites and since we do not control those Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those third party sites you visit.
Links & Data
For more information
For more information,please fill the form :Contact usOrSend an email
SEMCO Technologies South395, rue Louis Lépine / Parc du Millénaire34000 Montpellier, FrancePhone : + 33 (0)4 67 99 47 47Fax : + 33 (0)4 67 99 47 48 SEMCO Technologies North25, rue Didier Daurat / Parc Mermoz34170 Castelnau-le-lez, FrancePhone : + 33 (0)4 67 61 09 90Fax : + 33 (0)4 67 52 69 63
Baseline
Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - © 2018 SEMCO TECHNOLOGIES TM
- Designed by NEA
